My name is Chen Zhixuan
My name is Ma Weixian
Jiang Xiaomeng
Wang Ruijian
Zhou Guorui
My name is Sun Mingyang
Bai Guanyu
Zhang Ziyu
Love without pandering
Delicate details are seen
Infinite Possibilities
My Stage
Nobody hiding around to scare me, right?
I should take a look.
Nope.
How come there's no one?
That gave me a fright.
Sorry, I just couldn't help laughing.
Hello.
Sun Mingyang.
Wang Ruijian.
Wang Ruijian, got it.
Please sit down.
Okay.
At the time I was hiding behind the door to scare Wang Ruijian.
And Wang Ruijian's was
so adorably dazed.
I consider myself a tough guy.
When I was walking over there,
I saw
Sun Mingyang's hand.
I knew he was going to scare me.
So I pretended to be scared by him.
But actually I'd already spotted him.
I've never told him this secret to this day.
He still thinks he successfully scared me.
Hello.
Behind that lectern...
No.
When I saw Sun Mingyang,
he was hiding behind the lectern.
Actually I'd already seen him.
I could see half his body.
So I thought this guy...
It's okay.
Okay.
Hello.
Haven't we met before?
I've seen you.
We're... you're...
You're from the Central Academy of Drama, Hosting major?
Yes, yes.
You're a directing major.
I'm from the directing class.
Nice to meet you.
The very first moment when I made eye contact with him,
I just feel like I've seen
this face before.
You know what I mean?
His face just looks really familiar,
because I often run into him at school.
I'm telling you, at our school,
he had the same personality too.
He just had tons of friends.
A lot of my friends knew him.
I don't know if you guys know this.
Back then he had long hair,
the artsy kind.
Like a full head of long hair,
like down to here.
Actually, I think, that hairstyle looked better on him.
When the fourth person comes in,
let's not say anything.
Let him speak first.
Let's wait for him to say hi, okay?
If you want to make it more abstract,
we could sit like this. You sit at the corner.
Let's sit like this.
I'll take this seat, right?
Yeah.
Like a triangle?
Sure.
Then let's do that.
Hi there.
Hello.
Please sit.
Your school uniform looks great.
Handsome, you look sharp, bro.
You first.
Hi there.
Everyone came in at once.
They let everyone in.
Hey there, senior!
No way, it's you!
Finally we meet.
It's been a while.
Ma Weixian.
Well, it's because he and I are
classmates at Shenzhen University.
He's my junior from school.
I met him at school.
But he never told me,
about this.
Because everyone calls me handsome.
But he's a senior.
The character 'senior' has one more stroke than 'handsome', so he's even more handsome.
Hi.
I think I've seen you online.
How does everyone know each other?
We haven't met.
No, we haven't.
Hello. Hello, sir.
Hello.
Hello, sir.
Any familiar faces here?
Nope.
Not at all. We're the only two who know each other here.
Okay, just us two.
Haven't seen you for long.
I remember you had long hair before, right?
Yeah.
We're from the same class year.
Same year.
Then let's sit together.
Sure, come on.
Sit.
Go ahead, sit, senior.
So who's the youngest?
Who's the youngest here?
I was born in 2006.
That young?
I'm 2005.
And you?
I'm 2003.
Which month?
May for me.
Then you must be the oldest.
I'm 2007.
2007, which month?
February.
Then shouldn't you be...
Probably not.
I'm 2003.
2003, and I'm 2004.
Right, he's 2004, and you are?
I'm 2002.
I was born in April 2006.
He's the oldest.
Big bro.
Stop it.
Big bro should take the head seat.
Big bro.
Come on.
Stop it.
Come on, big bro.
How did I end up the oldest?
Big bro, please take the head seat.
Actually.
We're like his left and right-hand men.
We were both born in 2003.
Why is there still an empty chair?
Yeah, I was wondering why one chair is still empty.
No idea.
Could it be for the teacher?
It's the teacher.
Quick.
Move away from that seat.
Hello, Sir.
Hello, everyone.
Sir, please sit down.
My seat is over here? Okay.
Okay, thank you.
Please have a seat.
Sir, so maybe,
first,
let's start with a self-introduction.
Introduce yourselves first. Yes.
Hello, Sir. My name is Jiang Xiaomeng.
It's like that "suddenly losing it" kind of vibe.
There's a special task here.
After the teacher enters the classroom,
during the conversation,
if a matching keyword comes up,
you have to imitate the corresponding animal.
Keyword, pet.
Animal, ape.
What's the one for dog?
Animal to imitate, wolf.
Lion.
I graduated from the Acting Department of Chongqing University.
I'm a Cancer.
And my personality...
I'm pretty sensitive.
And before, in school, I played in the University Games Division II basketball league,
and I studied ballroom dance for a few years.
Thank you, everyone.
Hello, Sir.
My name is Chen Zhixuan.
I'm Ma Weixian.
I was born in 2006,
and I'm currently studying Broadcasting at Shenzhen University.
My MBTI is INTP.
My favorite sport is soccer.
Okay, thank you, Sir.
Hello, Sir. My name is Wang Ruijian,
and I usually like sports.
I really love sports.
Basketball, horseback riding, archery, skiing...
I can do them all.
Anyway, right now,
whenever anything about sports comes up,
he has to jump in.
Right.
Yes.
Hello, Sir.
I'm Zhou Guorui.
I was born in April 2006.
I'm from Zhejiang.
I'm currently studying...
at Beijing Institute of Fashion Technology,
and my major is Art and Technology.
Compared to all of you,
I may not be a
trained acting student.
And my hobbies in my free time,
are playing basketball, and...
A sports fanatic.
That's one thing,
and I also like drawing,
and doing some cooking,
and doing some cooking.
Why are you hissing at me?
And also.
Like in my free time,
I draw and play basketball.
Okay, I'll stop there.
Soccer, basketball, volleyball.
Middle- and long-distance running, sprinting, running fast, high knees.
Okay, I'll stop messing with you.
Runing, high knees, small quick steps...
Alright.
Okay, take a break.
Come back.
I'm getting a bit dizzy.
I've noticed,
he's the athletic type.
So can you tell what it is?
From Jurassic Park.
A dinosaur.
A dinosaur?
Right.
Actually, a cute dinosaur.
Well, at least it's a cool dinosaur.
Thank you, Sir.
You're the date-and-year type.
Whenever a year or date comes up,
you have to react to it.
Right.
He always acts like an ostrich.
I think.
Very close.
Yes, very much so.
Here's my take.
Your cluck sounds like a hen's.
Under what circumstances,
does a hen make that sound?
Right after laying an egg.
Right.
Because it hurts.
A rooster crows.
So I got it wrong.
This brings up an element,
related to acting,
called life observation.
With life observation, you have to be specific,
and detailed.
Right.
Who wants to perform next?
I will!
A puppy.
A cute puppy.
See?
Everyone blurted it out at the same time,
a cute puppy.
So what does that mean?
Cute. That's a very accurate way of expressing it.
Because your externalized body language,
and your demeanor and expressions,
and how you interacted with everyone,
we can tell,
you're really having fun.
Right.
See? Very endearing, very cute.
This is what being specific means.
When you act in the future, you have to be specific.
Only when you're specific will people understand,
what you're trying to convey.
I was actually secretly a little pleased,
but I didn't want to show it.
I didn't want people to see how happy I was.
I wanted to play it cool a bit.
I.
Earlier, I was waving my hand like this,
because it's that viral internet meme.
But I found that a lot of them,
just couldn't get it.
So I thought,
Maybe I should just do the same as Wang Ruijian,
learn from him,
like a real sea lion,
I got down on the ground,
lay on the floor and balanced the ball,
and then they instantly got it.
I think maybe you still need to be more concrete,
when performing these things.
That's how everyone does it.
I know what you're imitating.
Spin around, and it
A sea lion!
An adorable little sea lion.
Then my turn.
Go ahead.
A chimpanzee.
A gorilla.
Yes, a gorilla.
For the chimp, you need to be more specific, more exaggerated.
For example, like this,
once you do that, right?
That chimp expression, right?
The mouth.
See? And think about yours just now.
Right?
Right.
How does a gorilla scratch someone?
And how does it scratch itself?
Gorillas scratch people the opposite way.
It scratches like this.
Right.
At the time I was actually thinking,
I thought it was pretty simple.
Isn't it just...
Don't gorillas do it like this?
But after the teacher explained,
I realized that both my
understanding of this stuff,
and my own thinking,
were still way too shallow.
So going forward, I definitely need to
listen carefully in class,
and learn more about acting.
Very attentive.
You have to pay attention to all these details.
Okay.
You know?
Alright.
Animal Imitation Training
is just one method.
All of this will subtly
influence your future creative work.
I got into the Central Academy of Drama in 1991.
At our first class,
when we met the teacher,
our teacher said,
I know exactly what you're all thinking.
Don't think you're such a big deal.
You may have gotten in out of sheer luck.
How many of you are here out of true passion,
to pursue this art of acting?
And how many of you,
are here for fame, fortune, and vanity,
entering this profession?
This is something all of you
need to think long and hard about.
It's been a pleasure
meeting you all in this way.
Next, we're coming to the Dream Theater.
Dream Theater.
So let's all head over,
shall we?
On to the next part, let's go.
Thank you, Sir.
Hello, Sirs, Madam.
Welcome to the Incomplete Summer Training Camp.
This session has eight students.
I've already met you all just now.
The duration of this Training Camp,
is one and a half months.
Over the coming time,
you will receive, some voice, diction, movement, and acting training,
and some comprehensive skills training.
I hope everyone,
this summer,
will gain friendship,
grow along the way,
and experience an adventure of youth.
Welcome, everyone.
Now let's have the two teachers
introduce themselves.
Hello, everyone.
I'm the acting teacher who will be
spending this month and a half with you.
My name is Tian Ye.
Let's get along from here on out.
Okay.
Hello, Miss Tian.
Hello there.
Hello, everyone.
I'm the Program Director of our Training Camp.
Over the next month and a half,
I will witness your growth.
I hope to see you,
go from being the green newcomers,
at the very beginning,
to truly becoming someone who can write on their resume,
'I want to become an outstanding actor'.
Thank you, Sir.
For the entire Training Camp,
We'll wait and see your performance, okay?
Okay.
Alright.
Well then,
we also have a little welcome ceremony.
Okay?
Please come up.
Who loves eating cake?
I love cake!
Everyone is staring at that cake now.
So pretty.
Let's take a group photo.
Okay, come on.
Three, two, one! Great.
Students,
let's take a few more shots.
Come on, let's move back.
Okay, three, two, one.
You scared me!
Alright.
Now, with your backs to me,
let's strike a pose,
pointing at the sky.
Three, two, one.
All done?
What's going on?
Why did the lights go out?
The breaker tripped.
Someone is moving.
Is this part of the plan?
What's happening?
Is there a surprise in store?
The cake fell over.
It's ruined, right?
Look here.
Over here.
A piece fell off here.
This... this is...
Who did it?
In that case,
I think it's kind of rude.
Why?
What's the reason behind it?
If this act was meant
to show off your personality,
then I hope you can take the initiative to admit it.
Who is it?
No one knows.
Fine.
I'll give you fifteen minutes.
After fifteen minutes,
I want to see the answer.
Who touched the cake?
Let's start deducing!
How bad is it?
This part was cut off.
Could there be a clue inside?
Did anyone actually take a bite?
Was it good?
It was good.
You're so greedy!
Don't tell me it was you?
I've got it!
Come on, let me smell everyone's fingers!
Look, they're smelling fingers for scents.
Because if you grabbed it with your fingers,
and your hands would be clean,
there'd be tissue in your pocket.
Whose pocket has tissue?
Right, us.
We need to empty our pockets.
Turn out your pockets now!
He's actually pretty good at noticing details.
I've got nothing either.
Yeah, there's tissue in my pocket, but it wasn't me.
Turn them out!
This is for wiping my sweat.
Nothing at all.
Let me smell your hand.
Nothing there, right?
His hand smells like flowers!
I think it's him.
Very suspicious.
Who's framing me?
Who's setting me up?
Let me take a sniff.
This one's not bad.
Not too sweet.
Come here, let me smell yours.
Smell it.
Do you think there's a milky scent?
No.
Just a tiny bit.
Are you the werewolf?
See? He's on the offensive.
He's trying to frame me as the werewolf.
When it happened,
who was next to you?
He was next to me.
And then he, and then he.
When it happened,
What were you doing?
I was asking him,
why the lights went out,
if they were really broken.
Yeah, they went out.
Hey, when the lights were out,
did you feel anyone moving on either side of you?
No, isn't the person next to me you?
Next to me...
I think my senior, must be innocent, because he was really scared at the time,
Right?
What I can be sure of is,
he never left my sight.
Are you sure it was one of us?
No, because I remember,
during the silhouette part,
everyone's heads were there,
and when we came back, everyone's heads were still there.
I don't think we can
keep vouching for each other like this,
because I think if we go by this alone,
then actually none of us, moved at all.
Right.
Do you think it could be a prank the teacher is pulling?
Possible.
I think so too.
I think it's Mr. Huang pulling a prank.
I think our conclusion is
that none of us moved.
None of us moved.
Right.
We can't let them...
Mislead us.
We need to stay united,
and trust each other.
Yes.
Bro, I trust you all!
Do we have a result?
I think it wasn't us,
it wasn't any of us eight who did it.
Right, Mr. Huang?
Are you sure?
Sure.
The prankster was me.
Right?
Guessed it.
We guessed it.
It was deliberately designed.
Actually, our
class has already begun.
During your investigation just now,
you observed, doubted,
questioned, those kinds of emotions.
This is training our
observation skills.
Okay, you remember,
that moment just now?
You had no idea,
what my surprise would be.
Then I did it again,
and you didn't react.
Completely different from last time.
That's memory training for you.
When I did that,
what was going through your mind?
It was sudden, unexpected.
Got startled.
This fresh memory
has to live inside you.
You have to be observant.
Observation is a crucial quality,
for a future professional actor.
Next,
we're moving on to
our next segment.
The next segment is
an exam for you.
With "Me" as the theme,
structure a story.
You have two hours to prepare.
Independently create an original performance, no longer than four minutes.
You may freely use props from the rehearsal hall.
When time's up, return to the theater,
for your performance.
Sirs will score each performance,
out of fifty points.
The three students with the highest scores,
will receive credit points as a reward.
Credit points will affect
your overall score in the Training Camp.
Good luck to all of you!
Thank you, Sir.
See you in a bit!
The topic is "Me".
The pressure is on!
I'm totally confused,
and a bit panicked too.
In such a short time,
how am I supposed to portray it?
How do I even approach this?
Honestly, I was really stunned.
It's like I didn't know what to do.
Because having to perform as myself,
I feel like I'm
in some ways,
the person who knows me the least.
I've actually never acted before.
I really can't
think of what to do.